<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Camille Walters</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Camille Walters</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>about me</title>
      <link>http://example.org/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/resume/</guid>
      <description>My resume can be downloaded in a PDF format here.
education Bachelor of Applied Science in Honors Mechatronics Engineering University of Waterloo Co-operative Program Graduated in April 2022 skills the languages i&amp;rsquo;ve worked with (from most experience to least experience) are
C# C++ C Python Java Go HTML, CSS, XML Javascript SQL YAML the frameworks and libraries I&amp;rsquo;ve used are
Unity NUnit testNG Azure Jenkins Ansible Hugo Jekyll Latex some of my other sills include</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>fun stuff i&#39;m working on</title>
      <link>http://example.org/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/projects/</guid>
      <description>If you want to check out some of the code I&amp;rsquo;ve written, check out my Github profile.
Custom Smart Home System This project aims to use primarily Arduino to create a customized, cost effective smart home, with the goal of being energy efficient and secure.
Personal Website The latest iteration of my personal website (the one you&amp;rsquo;re reading right now!) was created using the Hugo framework.
ideas without borders During the second half of my undergrad, I was involved in Engineers Without Borders on their podcast portfolio to create ideas without borders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>get in touch</title>
      <link>http://example.org/contactme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/contactme/</guid>
      <description>The best way to contact me is through email. You can reach me at
camille -dot- h -dot- walters -at- gmail -dot- com
Alternatively, you can find me on LinkedIn here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
